Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Artist Files, 1963-2004
  - Subseries E: Material Separated from Visuals Binders
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 5/14], undated (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 6/14], undated (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 7/14], undated (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2] [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Tsibi Geva [2/2] [From Binder Sleeve 1/1], undated (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Graciela Hasper [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Graciela Hasper [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Binder Sleeve 1/6], undated (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Binder Sleeve 2/6], undated (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Binder Sleeve 4/6], undated (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - K.H. Hodicke; Koberling [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Kuitca [1] [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Kuitca [1] [From Binder Sleeve 5/30], undated (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 26/30], undated (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 27/30], undated (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 28/30], undated (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 29/30], undated (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Kuitca [1] [Binder Sleeve 30/30], undated (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Kuitca [1] [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Kuitca [2] [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Binder Sleeve 1/12], undated (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Binder Sleeve 2/12], undated (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Binder Sleeve 8/12], undated (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Binder Sleeve 9/12], undated (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - [Helmut] Middendorf [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Paul D. Miller/Gianmarco Montesano [Front Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Paul D. Miller/Gianmarco Montesano [Back Pocket], undated (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [From Binder Sleeve 3/8], undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [Binder Sleeve 5/8], undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [Binder Sleeve 6/8], undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Sabrina Mirri; Schifano [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Stephen Mueller [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Stephen Mueller [Binder Sleeves], undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Stephen Mueller [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Shirin Neshat Inventory [Loose Material], undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Shirin Neshat Inventory [Binder Sleeve 2/2], undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Shirin Neshat Inventory [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Loose Material], undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 2/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 3/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 9/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 10/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 11/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 12/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 13/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 14/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 15/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 16/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 18/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 19/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Binder Sleeve 20/20], undated (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Donald Newman [1/2] [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Donald Newman [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 1/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Donald Newman [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 2/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Donald Newman [2/2] [From Binder Sleeve 4/7], undated (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Donald Newman [2/2] [From Binder Sleeve 5/7], undated (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Donald Newman [2/2] [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Nunzio [Binder Sleeve 1/6], undated (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Nunzio [Binder Sleeve 6/6], undated (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Nunzio [From Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [From Binder Sleeve 1/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 3/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 5/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 6/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 7/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Binder Sleeve 8/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Manuel Ocampo [Back Pocket] [1/2], undated (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Manuel Ocampo [Back Pocket] [2/2], undated (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Manuel Ocampo [Loose Folder "Ocampo" in Binder], undated (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Palmieri Paladino [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 10/12], undated (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Palmieri Paladino [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 11/12], undated (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Palmieri Paladino [1/2] [From Binder Sleeve 12/12], undated (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2] [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2] [From Binder Sleeve 3/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2] [Binder Sleeve 13/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2] [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Liliana Porter [Loose Material], undated (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Liliana Porter [From Binder Sleeve 1/4], undated (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Liliana Porter [From Binder Sleeve 2/4], undated (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Liliana Porter [From Binder Sleeve 4/4], undated (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Sy Ross, Tod Wizon, Ira Richer [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Sy Ross, Tod Wizon, Ira Richer [Loose Folder], undated (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - Sy Ross, Tod Wizon, Ira Richer [Back Pocket] [Photos from Envelope and Exhibition Cards], undated (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Binder Sleeve 1/8], undated (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Cheri Samba, undated (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - Cheri Samba [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - Teresa Serrano [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - Teresa Serrano [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - Marco Tirelli; Flechemuller [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - Marco Tirelli; Flechemuller [From Binder Sleeve 10/13], undated (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - Marco Tirelli; Flechemuller [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - Jenny Watson [From Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Subseries F: Polaroids
    Series comprises Polaroid instant photographs from a box labeled "Polaroids."
    Polaroid photographs were originally sorted with dividers. The original order has been maintained, including the dividers. The labels of the dividers have been preserved here. Where Polaroids from one artist were found under another artist's label, or when there are no labeled dividers (as in the beginning of Binder BC), the artist's name has been provided in brackets by the archivist to aid the researcher.
    - [Stephen Mueller], undated (Album BC)
    - [Emily Cheng], undated (Album BC)
    - A, undated (Album BC)
    - Appel, undated (Album BC)
    - B, undated (Album BC)
    - Brauntuch, undated (Album BC)
    - Bowen, undated (Album BC)
    - Bowes, undated (Album BC)
    - Brenner, undated (Album BC)
    - Ceccobelli, undated (Album BC)
    - Chia, undated (Album BD)
    - Commandeur, undated (Album BD)
    - Condo, undated (Album BD)
    - Connelly, undated (Album BD)
    - Sold Connelly's, undated (Album BD)
    - D, undated (Album BE)
    - Duclos, undated (Album BE)
    - F, undated (Album BE)
    - Forg, undated (Album BE)
    - Galan, undated (Album BE)
    - Gallace, undated (Album BE)
    - Kaufmann, undated (Album BE)
    - Koberling, undated (Album BE)
    - Jannis Kounellis, undated (Album BE)
    - K, undated (Album BE)
    - Kuitca, undated (Album BE)
    - Hodgkins, undated (Album BF)
    - Joseph Kosuth, undated (Album BF)
    - G. Lang, undated (Album BF)
    - Tomarchio Levi, undated (Album BF)
    - Mattiacci, undated (Album BF)
    - McCollum, undated (Album BF)
    - [Mariani], undated (Album BF)
    - Middendorf/Sold Middendorf, undated (Album BF)
    - Mirri, undated (Album BG)
    - Moses, undated (Album BG)
    - Mueller, undated (Album BG)
    - [Robert Morris], undated (Album BG)
    - Newman, undated (Album BH)
    - Nunzio, undated (Album BH)
    - [Mueller], undated (Album BH)
    - Ocampo, undated (Album BH)
    - Ongaro, undated (Album BH)
    - Paladino, undated (Album BH)
    - Palmieri, undated (Album BH)
    - R [Gert Rappenecker], undated (Album BH)
    - Rayberry, undated (Album BH)
    - Pizzi Cannella, undated (Album BH)
    - Rammellzee, undated (Album BH)
    - Ross, undated (Album BI)
    - Rifka, undated (Album BI)
    - Salvo, undated (Album BI)
    - Cheri Samba, undated (Album BI)
    - Schuyff, undated (Album BI)
    - Sicilia, undated (Album BI)
    - Stevens, undated (Album BI)
    - Sonneman, undated (Album BI)
    - Tirelli, undated (Album BI)
    - T/Welsh, undated (Album BI)
    - Salomé, undated (Album BI)
    - Wizon, undated (Album BI)
    - Kruger, undated (Album BI)
    - Welling/[Elizondo], undated (Album BI)
- Series IV: Jean-Michel Basquiat Artist File, 1981-2003
  Series comprises artist bios and other promotional material, price lists, invoices, correspondence, phone bills, bank account records, photographic material, and periodicals and clipping relating to Jean-Michel Basquiat, his work, and his relationship with the Annina Nosei Gallery.
  - Subseries A: Artist Files
    - Basquiat - Misc. Receipts, Tel. Bil, 1981-1983 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Basquiat Bio, Press Release, Prices, 1981-1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Press, 1981-1992 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - [Exhibition Cards and Announcements], 1982-2003 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - "Poems by JMB", undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence
    Correspondence mostly regarding Basquiat and Basquiat work. Three small pieces of correspondence from Basquiat.
    - Basquiat Correspondence 1982-1987 [1/2] [Material from Plastic Sleeve], 1982, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Contains two letters signed by Basquiat.
    - Basquiat Correspondence 1982-1987 [2/2] (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Basquiat - Museums, 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - [Postcard Purportedly from Basquiat], undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Subseries C: Accounting
    - [Loose Material from "Basquiat Accounting" Letter Box], 1982 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [From "Basquiat Accounting" Letter Box] [1/3], 1981-1983 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - [Contents of Plastic Sleeve from "Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [1/3]"], 1981, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [From "Basquiat Accounting" Letter Box] [2/3], 1982 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [From "Basquiat Accounting" Letter Box] [3/3], 1982 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Invoices
    - [Basquiat - Invoices] [1/4], 1981, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - [Basquiat - Invoices] [2/4], 1982, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - [Basquiat - Invoices] [3/4], 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - [Basquiat - Invoices] [4/4], 1983-1987 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Subseries E: Slides Binder
    Original binder sleeves, when numbered, are included with their contents in the new binders.
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat [Material from Front Pocket of Slide Binder], undated (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Slides, undated (Album BJ)
  - Subseries F: Visuals Binders
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [1/3], undated (Album BK)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [2/3], undated (Album BL)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [3/3], undated (Album BM)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [1/3], undated (Album BN)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [2/3], undated (Album BO)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [3/3], undated (Album BP)
  - Subseries G: Material Separated from Visuals Binders
    The order of folders in this subseries follows the order of binders in Series IV, Subseries F.
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [1/3] [From Binder Sleeve 5/17], undated (Box 35, Folder 73)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book I [3/3] [From Binder Sleeve 13/22], undated (Box 35, Folder 74)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [Front Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 75)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [3/3] [From Binder Sleeve 23/29], undated (Box 35, Folder 76)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [3/3] [From Binder Sleeve 24/29], undated (Box 35, Folder 77)
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Book II [Back Pocket], undated (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - Subseries H: Polaroids
    - Basquiat Polaroids, undated (Album BQ)
  - Subseries I: Catalogs
    - [Catalogs] [1/3], 1982, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - [Catalogs] [2/3], 1989-1996 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - [Catalogs] [3/3], undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Subseries J: Periodicals, Clippings
    Subseries arranged chronologically.
    - [Basquiat - Loose Clippings], 1982-1998 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - [Periodicals] [1/4], 1983 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - [Periodicals] [2/4], 1983-1988 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - [Periodicals] [3/4], 1992 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - [Periodicals] [4/4], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Series V: Exhibition Records, 1980-2009
  Series comprises materials related to each show held at the Annina Nosei Gallery. Materials include installation photographs, price lists, artist bios, exhibition cards, press clippings, catalogs, and guest books.
  Exhibition Records: Subseries A-G comprise what the gallery termed "Exhibition Records," a term denoting all materials produced and collected in connection with a specific exhibition. These records were originally sleeved in binders. Material has been removed from binder sleeves and binders and placed in folders and boxes. Titles of binders have been retained in the titles of subseries.
  Materials in these subseries are arranged in the order in which they were filed in their original binders, which is reverse chronological order for each binder. The binders (subseries) themselves have been ordered chronologically by the archivist.
  Each folder represents a specific exhibition (e.g., all of the material relating to the Barbara Kruger March 5-26, 1983 show is put into one folder), regardless of how many binder sleeves the material orignally occupied. Most binders were accompanied by a list of binder contents listing the exhibitions included in the date range for that binder. These lists, where available, were used by the archivist to create folder titles. Where these lists were absent, the archivist has supplied folder titles by referring to the chronological lists found in the yearly catalogs for the gallery.
  Some consecutive exhibitions are represented by very little material. In such a case, that material is placed in a single folder, which is labelled with the artists' names and show titles separated by semicolons (e.g., "[Stephen Mueller; Keith Milow; Group Show; Keith Haring]").
  Catalogs: Subseries H comprises catalogs created by the gallery to accompany each exhibition.
  Guest Books: Subseries I comprises guest books signed by gallery patrons.
  - Subseries A: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; 1982-1983, 1983-1984
    - [Front Pocket], undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - [Summer Group Show], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - [Helmut Middendorf], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - [Group Show; Apr 14 - May 4 1984] (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - [David Bowes "Drawings"], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - [Barbara Kruger], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - [David Bowes "Capriccios"], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - [Sabina Mirri], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - [European Expressions], 1983 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - [Group Show; Nov 5, 1983] (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - [Ira Richer], 1983 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - [Group Show; June 11 - July 29, 1983] (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - [K.H. Hodicke], 1983 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - [Athos Ongaro], 1983 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - [Francois Boisrond], 1983 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - [Barbara Kruger], 1983 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - [Kenny Scharf], 1983 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - [Mario Schifano], 1983 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - [Selected Works; Dec 16 - Jan 6, 1983] (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - [Jean-Michel Basquiat], 1982 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - [Stephen Mueller; Keith Milow; Group Show; Keith Haring], 1981, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - [David Deutsch], 1981 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - [Group Show; March 1981] (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - [Kim Gordon at White Columns], undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - [Drawings & Paintings on Paper], 1980 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - [American and Italian New Image Artists], 1981 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - [Mimmo Paladino], 1980 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - [Initial Group Show; May - June 1980] (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - [Unlabelled Polaroids from Binder Sleeve of Pre-gallery Curating], undated (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - [Annina Nosei Pre-gallery Curating], undated (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - [Back Pocket], 1980, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Subseries B: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; September 1984 - August 1986
    - [Front Pocket, including List of Binder Contents], 1986, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - [Group Show], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - [Pietro Fortuna], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - [Pizzi Cannella], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - [Claudio Palmieri], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - [Barbara Kruger], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - [Helmut Middendorf], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - [Basquiat "Paintings from 1982"], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - [Chuck Connelly], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - [Vincent Gallo], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 41)
    - ["Drawing the Line - Painting"], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - ["The Door"], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 43)
    - [Sabina Mirri], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 44)
    - [Francois Boisrond], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 45)
    - [Ira Richer], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 46)
    - [Nunzio], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 47)
    - [Pizzi Cannella], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 48)
    - [Marco Tirelli], 1985 (Box 48, Folder 49)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 50)
    - [Karel Appel], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 51)
    - [Chuck Connelly], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 52)
    - [Georges Rousse], 1984 (Box 48, Folder 53)
  - Subseries C: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; October 1986 to December 1989 (included [sic]
    - [List of Binder Contents], undated (Box 48, Folder 54)
    - [Mary Obering] (Box 48, Folder 55)
    - [Works on Paper], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 56)
    - [Ronald Gault Jirado], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 57)
    - [Group Show], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 58)
    - [Group Exhibition to Benefit the AIDS Crisis], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 59)
    - [Christiane Richter], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 60)
    - [Beth Brenner], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 61)
    - [Gary Lang], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 62)
    - [Julio Galan], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 63)
    - [ARCO], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 64)
    - [Ellen Brooks], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 65)
    - [Helmut Middendorf], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 66)
    - [Jean-Michel Basquiat Memorial Exhibition], 1988 (Box 48, Folder 67)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1989 (Box 48, Folder 68)
    - ["Metathesis"], 1988 (Box 48, Folder 69)
    - [Vincent Gallo], 1988 (Box 48, Folder 70)
    - ["Mutations"], 1988 (Box 48, Folder 71)
    - [Mary Oberling], 1988 (Box 48, Folder 72)
    - [Group Show], 1988 (Box 48, Folder 73)
    - [Alan McCollum], 1988 (Box 48, Folder 74)
    - [Vincent Gallo], 1988 (Box 48, Folder 75)
    - ["Fragments"], 1988 (Box 48, Folder 76)
    - [Ellen Brooks], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 77)
    - [Beth Brenner], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 78)
    - [Rotating Photography], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 79)
    - ["Spatial-FX"], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 80)
    - [Chuck Connelly], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 81)
    - [Andy Moses], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 82)
    - [Tod Wizon], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 83)
    - [Nunzio], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 84)
    - [Group Show], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 85)
    - [Ira Richer], 1987 (Box 48, Folder 86)
    - [Group Show], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 87)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 88)
    - [Vincent Gallo], 1986 (Box 48, Folder 89)
  - Subseries D: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; January 1990 - July 1992
    - [List of Binder Contents], undated (Box 48, Folder 90)
    - [Specs Photography], 1992 (Box 48, Folder 91)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1992 (Box 48, Folder 92)
    - [Julio Galan], 1992 (Box 48, Folder 93)
    - [Sal Scarpitta], 1992 (Box 48, Folder 94)
    - [Works on Paper], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 95)
    - [Cheri Samba], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 96)
    - [Jenny Watson], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 97)
    - [Gian Marco Montesano], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 98)
    - [Internationale Contemporanea], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 99)
    - [Guillermo Kuitca], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 100)
    - ["Landscape Painting"], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 101)
    - [Nancy Bowen, Gary Lang], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 102)
    - ["Personal Portraits"], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 103)
    - [Helmut Middendorf], 1991 (Box 48, Folder 104)
    - [Stephen Mueller], 1990 (Box 48, Folder 105)
    - [Tsibi Geva], 1990 (Box 48, Folder 106)
    - [Julio Galan], 1990 (Box 48, Folder 107)
    - [Cheri Samba], 1990 (Box 48, Folder 108)
    - [Gary Lang], 1990 (Box 48, Folder 110)
    - [Guillermo Kuitca], 1990 (Box 48, Folder 111)
    - [Group Show], 1990 (Box 48, Folder 112)
  - Subseries E: Exhibitions; October 1992 - Jan 1993 - 94 - 96
    - [Front Pocket, Including List of Binder Contents], undated (Box 48, Folder 113)
    - [Helmut Middendorf; Stephen Mueller; Manuel Ocampo; Paul D. Miller], 1996, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 114)
    - [Summer Group Show Exhibition; Julio Galan; Arturo Elizondo; Ghada Amer; Danielle Galliano], 1996 (Box 48, Folder 115)
    - [Unlabelled Folder of Exhibition], undated (Box 48, Folder 116)
    - [Athos Ongaro; Inaugural Exhibition], 1995, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 117)
    - [Shirin Neshat; Summer Invitational], 1995 (Box 48, Folder 118)
    - [Arturo Duclos; Flechmuller; Kocheisen + Hullmann; Tsibi Geva], 1995 (Box 48, Folder 119)
    - [Anna Paparatti], 1994 (Box 48, Folder 120)
    - [Cheri Samba; Teresa Serrano, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 121)
    - [Studio Annina Nosei Roma], 1994 (Box 48, Folder 122)
    - [Jenny Watson; Group Exhibition], 1994 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - [Arturo Duclos; Manuel Ocampo; Flechemuller], 1994 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - [Stephen Mueller Group Exhibition], 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - [Kocheisen + Hullmann; Quotes from Past Exhibitions; Nancy Bowen], 1993 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - ["Continuing Generations"], 1993 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - ["7 Latin American Artists"], 1993 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - [Tsibi Geva], 1993 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - [Arturo Duclos], 1993 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - [Pizzi Cannella], 1993 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - [Group Exhibition], 1993 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - [Jenny Watson], 1992 (Box 49, Folder 11)